Let's see if your fists are faster
or my gun.
Wang Wenhao
What you wanted is right here
Now let Ruo Jin go
No!
Saving the damsel, huh?
Fine, fine, fine
Today, I'll let you play the hero
I won't do anything to Ruo Jin
After all, our wedding's just around the corner
Wang Wenhao
Cut the crap
If you've got the guts, come at me
Using a woman to threaten me
You're a spineless coward
Tie him up, now!
No!
Search him
Gu Yuan
Don't worry about us
Go help Feifan, quickly
Getting you to a safe place
is helping Feifan.
Don't worry
Once we get through this crisis
Premier Medical Hall
you'll be back soon
Feifan!
Feifan! Feifan! Feifan!
Wang Wenhao!
The Wangs won't stay untouchable forever.
After a scene this big,
the police will track you down in no time.
Ruo Jin,
you're my fiancee.
If anything really goes down,
do you think you can escape?
Feifan!
Feifan, don't listen to him!
Ruo Jin,
get out of here!
Wang Wenhao,
you already have me tied up here.
Why not just take Ruo Jin and leave?
Are you trying to die with me?
Ren Feifan,
you eyesore.
Finally, you'll be out of my sight.
Oh,
by the way,
let me show you who this is.
Mommy, where are you?
Yixin!
When can I come play with you?
Let's go to the amusement park with Daddy.
Wang Wenhao,
what did you do to Yixin?
What did you do to Yixin?!
Ren Feifan,
if you dare try anything funny,
I'll send Yixin down to keep you company.
Wang Wenhao,
don't make me kill you.
You want to kill me?
Come on!
Kill me!
Ren Feifan,
see you in the next life.
Feifan!
Move!
Let me go!
Feifan! Feifan!
Feifan!
Hurry up and untie the ropes on my back!
Why didn't you wait until I was blown up?
I wish I could have.
Wang Wenhao, let me go!
Let me go!
I want to die! I want to die with Feifan!
I wanted you to watch him die
so you'd give up hope and just marry me.
Get her inside.
No! Let me go! Let me go!
Untie it faster!
We planned for everything,
but we still missed a step.
Let's go!
Dad,
the biggest threat has now been eliminated.
You don't have to worry anymore
about anyone in North City toppling us.
But the old man from the Ren family
is still missing.
That means Ren Feifan had accomplices.
Come on, Dad,
you're overthinking it.
At most, they sensed danger and hid.
Maybe they've gone off the grid
and will never come back.
Send someone to keep investigating.
I don't like leaving loose ends.
That temper of yours will get you killed one day.
Come on, Dad,
my wedding to Ruo Jin is right around the corner.
Lighten up a little!
Sit.
Close your eyes.
What is it?
Look.
It's beautiful.
Do you like it?
I love it.
Let me put it on for you.
It looks stunning.
I wish I could wear it on our wedding day too.
As my lady commands.
What are you doing here?
I came to see you.
White is unlucky.
Gemstones suit you better.
Does it look good?
Beautiful.
Xu Ruo Jin.
Are you here for the wedding, Miss Shen?
Others come bearing gifts.
You came to hand out slaps.
What are you talking about?
Xu Ruo Jin.
Are you really going to marry him?
I'm marrying Wenhao because I love him.
I want to.
Miss Shen, if you're here for the wedding,
you're most welcome.
If not,
please leave.
I never thought you were this kind of person.
I was so wrong about you.
Miss Shen.
This way, please.
Ruo Jin.
Feifan.
Let me see if you're hurt anywhere.
Ruo Jin, I'm fine.
Just listen to me first.
Tomorrow, attend Wang Wenhao's wedding.
Then see which of his people aren't there.
Gu Yuan and I will track his movements.
We should be able to find Yixin's location.
Got it.
I'll play it by ear when the time comes.
The wedding is about to begin.
Let's give a warm round of applause
to welcome the bride and groom.
Yes!
Happily united in marriage
A hundred years of harmony
First, I'd like to thank everyone here
for attending my wedding with Ruo Jin.
Ruo Jin and I have been through so much together,
and it wasn't easy getting to this day.
So I want to say to Ruo Jin,
I promise to be a good husband,
and protect you for a lifetime.
Next, I want to thank my father.
Without his hard work in raising me,
there would be no Wang Wenhao today.
Finally,
I want to thank all of you here
for being here today
to witness a new start for the Wangs,
a new era.
In the near future, Wang Pharmaceutical
will launch a drug that'll stun the world.
Recently, some people got jealous,
coveting our new product,
constantly trying to sabotage it.
In the end, it was all in vain.
They only ended up hurting themselves.
If any of you here support us
and partner with Wang Pharmaceutical,
we're willing to offer shares.
Besides getting a piece of the pie,
we can also give everyone here
a chance to go down in history.
Alright.
The groom may now kiss the bride.
Kiss her!
How's the progress lately?
We're speeding it up.
Make sure to hurry.
Understood.
How could this be?
Who did this? How could anyone do this?
My God, this is outrageous!
So inhumane!
Unbelievable, how cruel!
How did these things end up here?
Isn't this a crime?
Someone!
Shut it off!
So this is what you called
the new drug that would stun the world?
Ren Feifan!
How can this be?
How are you...
Still alive, right?
Wang Wenhao,
looks like your bomb didn't quite work.
What are you saying?
I have no idea what you mean.
I showed up right at your moment of triumph.
Must be a tough pill to swallow, right?
As you can all see,
this is how Wang Group developed the drug.
They kidnapped patients for live testing,
causing multiple deaths.
And their so-called miracle cure-all drug
actually has no such effect.
Don't believe him, everyone!
This is all fake!
Everything he's saying is fake!
Seems young Mr. Wang still won't admit it.
That's alright.
I have more evidence.
Take a look.
These are all imported instruments.
Can you afford it if you break them?
Get back to work, all of you.
Mr. Wang, the experiment next door is starting.
Radiation is high. You should step away.
The new drug developed by Wang Group
is an unfinished product from my youth.
After my parents talked to me,
I realized this drug is highly unstable
and can cause severe side effects.